{
  "title": "American History - Places",
  "path": "KnowledgeBowl/",
  "data": [
    {
      "questionType": "Drill and Kill",
      "question": "Places",
      "items": [
        {
          "question": "When did the first Pilgrims arrive in Massachusetts?",
          "answer": "1620"
        },
        {
          "question": "When was Manhattan Island founded?",
          "answer": "1625"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "Drill and Kill",
      "question": "Places",
      "items": [
        {
          "question": "What famous island in New York is surrounded by two rivers?",
          "answer": "Manhattan Island"
        },
        {
          "question": "What was Manhattan Island originally called?",
          "answer": "New Amsterdam"
        },
        {
          "question": "What 2 ski resorts are in Big Cottonwood Canyon?",
          "answer": "Brighton, Solitude"
        },
        {
          "question": "Which English colony was the first to succeed?",
          "answer": "Jamestown"
        },
        {
          "question": "What colony did the Pilgrims establish?",
          "answer": "Plymouth Colony"
        },
        {
          "question": "What rock did the Pilgrims land on?",
          "answer": "Plymouth Rock"
        },
        {
          "question": "Where is the Alamo?",
          "answer": "Texas"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "Drill and Kill",
      "question": "Places",
      "items": [
        {
          "question": "What trail went from Santa Fe to Los Angles, CA?",
          "answer": "Old Spanish Trail"
        },
        {
          "question": "A 2000 miles trapper trail from Independence, Missouri to Idaho to the west coast?",
          "answer": "Oregon Trail"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "Drill and Kill",
      "question": "Places",
      "items": [
        {
          "question": "What two battles started the Revolutionary War between England and America?",
          "answer": "Battle of Concord, Battle of Lexington"
        },
        {
          "question": "What did the colonists do when the English taxed their tea? ",
          "answer": "Boston Tea Party"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "Drill and Kill",
      "question": "Places",
      "items": [
        {
          "question": "What was mail delivered on horse back called?",
          "answer": "Pony Express"
        },
        {
          "question": "What put the Pony Express out of business?",
          "answer": "The telegraph"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "Drill and Kill",
      "question": "Places",
      "items": [
        {
          "question": "What cities did the Pony Express trail run from?",
          "answer": "St. Joseph, Missouri to Sacramento, CA"
        },
        {
          "question": "What famous party was stranded in the Sierra Nevadaâ€™s and nearly starved to death?",
          "answer": "Donner Party"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who fought over the Alamo?",
          "answer": "Mexico and Texans"
        },
        {
          "question": "Who died at the Alamo?",
          "answer": "All were killed"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "Drill and Kill",
      "question": "Places",
      "items": [
      ]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "Drill and Kill",
      "question": "Places",
      "items": [
      ]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "Drill and Kill",
      "question": "Places",
      "items": [
      ]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "Drill and Kill",
      "question": "Places",
      "items": [
      ]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "Drill and Kill",
      "question": "Places",
      "items": [
      ]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "Drill and Kill",
      "question": "Places",
      "items": [
      ]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "Drill and Kill",
      "question": "Places",
      "items": [
      ]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "Drill and Kill",
      "question": "Places",
      "items": [
      ]
    }
  ]
}